http://www.bsc-ind.com/privacy-statement/

Contact
Search for:
Privacy Policy
BSC Industries, Inc. is committed to providing a secure website for our visitors. This privacy statement is provided to assist you in understanding our practices concerning cookies and personal information you may supply when visiting this site.
BSC Industries, Inc. respects your privacy. We do not sell or rent to any third-party any personally identifiable information. Our website and ads may utilize first- and third-party cookies and similar technologies to provide enhanced features, remember user preferences, for analytics, product development, and market research purposes. This information is used in aggregate to provide a better user experience. Information you provide through contact forms will be used to correspond with you regarding specific inquiries or to send you promotional emails you have requested.
The web servers we use are designed for internet commerce and utilize industry standard methods of protecting the security of information sent over the site. Each page of the BSC Industries, Inc. site on which information is exchanged between you and our company employs Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) technology.
Our website contains links to other sites that are owned and operated by third-parties such as our supplier partners. These third-party sites have their own privacy statements. BSC Industries, Inc. is not responsible for these statements.
BSC Industries, Inc. may update this policy from time to time. Updates will be posted on the website and will be effective as of the date of posting. Please check the website periodically for updates.
By continuing to visit or interact with our website, you consent to the use of cookies and similar technologies as described in this privacy policy.
© 2018 BSC Industries, Inc.
